{
    "subject": "resource/Eugenio_Mar\u00eda_de_Hostos",
    "predicate": "ontology/occupation",
    "object": "resource/Intellectual",
    "human_readable": "Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos' occupation is Intellectual.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.916589617729187,
            "question": "What was Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8811051249504089,
            "question": "What impact did Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos have as an Intellectual?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8807585835456848,
            "question": "What is meant by the term 'Intellectual' in relation to Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8373667001724243,
            "question": "Why is it important to recognize and value individuals like Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos who were Intellectuals?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8141694068908691,
            "question": "How is Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos remembered today based on his occupation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.763972282409668,
            "question": "Were there any particular challenges faced by Intellectuals like Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos during his time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5617859959602356,
            "question": "Describe the type of work Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos was known for."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4980120062828064,
            "question": "What field did Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos work in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2783680856227875,
            "question": "What qualities are typically associated with the role of an 'Intellectual'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23270630836486816,
            "question": "Can you give examples of the types of activities an 'Intellectual' might be involved in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos' occupation is Intellectual.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5856_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What qualities are typically associated with the role of an 'Intellectual'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5856_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field did Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos work in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5856_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Describe the type of work Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos was known for.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5856_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5856_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5856_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5856_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5856_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5856_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5856_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5856_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5856_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5856_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5856_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n**Explanation:**\n\nThe provided text documents consistently refer to Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos as a \"writer, intellectual,\"  \"intellectual,\" and \"philosopher\". This strongly supports the claim that his occupation was an Intellectual. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Eugenio Mar\u00eda de Hostos was an intellectual. The context mentions that he was a \u201cPuerto Rican writer, intellectual, journalist, educator, liberator, and sociologist,\u201d which confirms his occupation as an intellectual."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}